= www.kisskh.asia =
♪Her smile, her kindness, her kiss♪
♪Her presumptions♪
♪She was in love, she was tired, she walked away♪
♪Only tears remained♪
♪Can't hold on, can't forget♪
♪Can't let go of her all-or-nothing love♪
♪Promises became a burden after all that hesitation♪
♪Leaving longing frozen into a winter night♪
♪That girl, my girl♪
♪The light's still on, but you're already far away♪
♪The words reach my lips, but I can't get them out♪
♪That girl, my girl♪
♪My voice echoes, but no one answers♪
♪Is this really how it ends for us?♪
[You don't have to be perfect tobe worthy of Love]
[The Early Spring]
[Adapted from The Early Spring on jjwxc.net, Author: Gu Niang Bie Ku]
[Episode 2]
[The Workplace Isn't Some Kind of Child's Play]
Help!
Let me open the door.
Sorry.
It's all my fault.
I was taking a shower and didn't hear my phone ring.
The landlord told me
a new tenant would be coming tonight.
I forgot to inform Tao
and caused her to mistake you for some hooligan.
Sorry.
It's my fault.
I should've waited for her to enter the house before coming up.
Actually, I could feel that you were scared,
so I didn't enter the lift.
I didn't expect
that I would still scare you.
Sorry.
That's not it.
I was way too timid.
I probably scared you too.
I even
broke two bottles of your sauce.
It's fine.
Well,
I am Sun Yuanzhu.
Sun Yu.
Hello.
Shang Zhitao.
It's normal to have a boy as a flatmate in Beijing.
Don't worry.
I'll interrogate him later.
Wow.
You have so many types of seasoning.
You can cook too?
Just simple meals.
I'll make something for you two if I get the chance.
That's exactly what I'm waiting for.
Do you need any help?
No need.
Do you work at BAT?
Yes. I work in the IT industry.
A rising star in the tech industry.
I work for an online dating company.
Find me if you need anything.
Sure.
Tao.
An advertising elite working in Lime.
Lime?
Lime is amazing.
Those who work there are all incredible.
Not at all.
I just got hired.
Just a rookie.
When you've survived the initial phase,
you'll be a proven elite.
When I started working,
I spent a whole night at the convenience store entrance editing my slides.
I was even mistaken for an oden thief.
An oden thief?
What was your name again?
Zhu.
Sun Yuanzhu.
Sorry.
Is your name from the poem
"My lofty aspirations encompass the world;
My wings yearn to carry me to far-off heights?"
You actually know the poem?
My father taught it to me when I was young.
That's amazing.
I hereby announce
the completion of our temporary
three-man home.
It's late. Get your things sorted
and go to bed when you're done.
Tomorrow is Saturday.
Let's talk after we wake up.
Sure.
Good night.
After you.
I'll go in first.
Sorry.
After her.
Boss.
We lost the Qipai project.
Mr. Lin handed the project to Alex.
What?
Our project has been taken away by Division Two.
Boss, are you listening?
He agreed to the 30% discount and signed the contract?
I guess.
What an embarrassment.
I've embarrassed you.
I mean, Alex
is an embarrassment to Lime.
Exactly.
You've spent years
maintaining Qipai as a client.
We made the proposal
after staying up late for half a month.
Now, the project has been taken away from our hands.
Boss.
What should we do now?
If we can't
complete this month's KPI,
- we will... - Look.
Go and accept
the Mulanshuo e-commerce project.
Didn't you say to reject it?
That company has all kinds of issues.
They are even requesting a specific production team.
Great.
I hope you have other alternatives.
Which production team has the client requested?
Laiyu,
a production team in Guangzhou.
They have a new energy vehicle commercial
that went viral in the first half of the year.
They are quite popular among the southern media outlets.
They are not bad.
Have you contacted them?
I have.
They are very interested in working with us,
but their whole team is based in Guangzhou.
Give me the team's profile.
- Sure. - I'll leave the rest to you.
Sure.
Boss.
All the other employees are working on other projects.
Can I bring Shang Zhitao along
for this project?
She is patient and has a good temper.
No one else
in Lime is better than her at this.
Luke.
I won't quit.
Go ahead.
I also think she'll be helpful.
Helpful?
Honest
and single-minded.
How long will she last in the advertising industry?
Didn't you tell me
to go ahead?
[20,300 yuan has been deposited]
Mom.
Tao.
I transferred 16,000 yuan to you.
Did you receive it?
Are you sure it's 16,000 yuan?
Why did I receive
20,300 yuan instead?
Did the bank give me extra?
When I told your dad
to transfer you some money,
he didn't even hesitate.
He would give you a gold mine if he had one,
let alone the little bit of money he has now.
Why didn't you give us a call
after you arrived?
How are your food and accommodation?
Do you have enough money?
Which question should I answer first?
Calm down.
You can find a job slowly
until you find the right one.
Don't make do with your job.
If you can't find one, come home.
We'll support you.
Coming home is also a good choice.
Mom. Dad. I love you both so much.
Don't worry, both of you.
Your daughter has been impressive.
I'm now working at the biggest advertising company in China.
Of course, my daughter is impressive.
You joined a large company in Beijing as soon as you graduated.
Their revenue reaches billions of yuan.
I'm telling you.
The ancestors
of the Shang family
are more than proud of you.
Do you think an ordinary person is good enough for you?
No.
Absolutely not.
I have to go now.
My superior is looking for me.
Don't be too exhausted from working.
If your superior dares to bully you,
your mother and I will fly over
to protect you with sticks in our hands.
Got it.
I'm hanging up.
You're already...
She hung up.
Tao,
pack up.
We are going on a business trip.
We leave tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Come in.
Came to the office on a weekend?
It's rare for you to do that.
Alex's group stole your client, Qipai.
They're having a celebration dinner tonight.
They asked me to come over and arrange it.
They sell ideas as if they were street vendors.
I suggest you send their group
to the market.
It's not a bad idea.
I'll try to contact the market later.
Speaking of which,
in three months,
the company will appoint one of you two directors
as the acting general manager.
Sales KPI
is the most important assessment criterion.
I think
he probably has heard something about it.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have
dared to slash his price to steal your client.
I wish him success, then.
Look at this.
[Mulanshuo E-commerce TVC proposal]
[Business Division One]
Mulanshuo?
No wonder you are so calm.
Turns out, you've taken the Mulanshuo project.
However, their budget
is 20% higher than Qipai's.
This is a huge project.
I'm sure Lumi will be very busy.
Oh,
is she getting Shang Zhitao involved in the project, as well?
If you really care about her,
spare her some manpower.
It's urgent, and the workload is heavy.
A rookie won't be much help.
Got it.
When you're shooting the commercial,
I'll assign some people to help you.
Fine. I won't disturb you any longer.
I'll go contact the supermarket now.
I'm leaving.
[1.2 Core Competitiveness]
[2.1 Main Creative Team (1) Director: Li Wencai]
[(2) Main Outdoor Photography: Pan Weihao]
What time is your flight tomorrow?
Help me book a ticket.
[Guangzhou]
Flora.
You're so early.
Are you studying?
I'm just reading.
Luke, good morning.
Morning.
Do you want coffee?
I'm going to buy coffee.
Let me pay for it.
No need.
Don't try to use any street smarts.
It doesn't suit you.
This boss of mine
is handsome,
but he has a foul mouth.
[Guangzhou]
This is already the fourth brew.
- I'm going to order some liquor. - Thank you.
What's the meaning of this?
They said they were already on the way an hour ago.
Fooling around with me?
Calm down.
Calm down, you say?
Mr. Li.
It's been a while.
I didn't expect
you to come in person.
When I saw your name,
I wanted to pay you a visit.
Do you two know each other?
We do.
Luke is our team's benefactor.
Mr. Li, you flatter me.
Don't be so humble.
Four years ago,
if you hadn't kicked us out of the project,
our team wouldn't have achieved so many things now.
Don't bully a young person for being poor,
for he might turn into a dragon one day.
Don't believe it, and you'll be poor forever.
This has been our team's motto
for all these years.
I can't believe
I get to say it to you today.
I didn't look down on your team back then.
It's only a given
for you to achieve great things today.
Even if I could turn back time,
after much deliberation,
your team still wouldn't necessarily be the best choice.
I completely understand.
So, our team also did much deliberation
regarding your project today.
The project is not bad,
and the budget is high.
However, our team can't fit this project into our schedule.
Please find another team
for the commercial shoot.
Mr. Li,
you could've told us a day earlier that you were booked.
We wouldn't have had to fly all the way here
just to eat pork buns.
Consider it my treat.
Mr. Li,
if you change your mind,
let us know your conditions, thoughts, and requirements
up front.
We'll do our best to work with your team.
We purposely flew here for a collaboration.
If you are free, you may let us know.
We'll have a chance to work together in the future.
Should we go after him?
Go after him?
Just wait.
Luke.
Should we find another team as a backup?
A supply and demand relationship decides our bargaining chip.
Lumi,
help me look for the director they usually work with
and the brands they've recently worked with.
Got it.
He brought us here
just to gloat at Luke?
Let's do as Luke told us to for now.
I was wondering
why he insisted on coming when the attendant
does not share the same title as his.
Now, I know why.
He must have guessed this would happen.
With him around,
he must have a plan.
Can he deal with this?
Yes.
Do you trust him so much?
Of course.
When it comes to work,
he has always been reliable.
Sure.
Please send the relevant information to my inbox.
Thank you.
[Laiyu's information]
[Tian Zheng's personal information]
[Want to become an extra? Tian Zheng is shooting a commercial. Join now!]
[Requirements for extras]
Laiyu is indeed an excellent team on the rise.
They've worked on 70%
of all popular brands' commercial shoots.
All new production teams will experience a bottleneck.
Have they done any international tier-one brands' commercials?
No.
Give me a list
of all international clients of Lime in Guangzhou.
Swapping resources.
Yes.
What about Taobao?
There's also a new automobile brand from Germany.
Not long ago, they tried to secure a partnership with Tmall,
but they failed.
Look.
Go and focus on getting the Taobao project.
All right.
Where's Shang Zhitao?
What are you doing?
We are going to brief the extras.
Why are you running around?
Get back immediately.
Sure.
That scene just now. I think...
[Lumi]
Flora, where are you?
Lumi.
I...
I'm at Laiyu's filming set.
Filming set?
I'm here as an extra.
I saw the director just now.
I wanted to see
if I could get something out of him.
Use this opportunity to ask the director.
Tell him
you have a Taobao project to work on.
Ask him if he's interested.
I...
Can I ask him directly?
Ask him directly.
I'll take full responsibility if something happens.
No one will blame you.
All right.
It was an exciting performance.
I'll call everyone here at lunchtime
to talk about
our filming plan in the future.
For the next scene...
Director,
I am Shang Zhitao from Lime Advertising.
Hello.
Not bad.
I didn't expect you to be so smart.
I thought I couldn't help much.
Since Luke wanted to know more about the director,
I rushed to the set to take a look.
Lumi.
Why aren't
both of them speaking to each other?
It's fine.
He knows what to do.
You went over my head
and spoke to the director immediately.
Impressive.
Do you think I can't deal with your trick?
Mr. Li,
in business,
we always have to look forward.
If this project is a success,
and the filming of the commercial is completed,
your team will truly
be the best commercial production team in Guangzhou.
However, if you're stuck in the past
and give up on a top-tier client,
it won't be worth it.
I'm betting
that within ten seconds,
Mr. Li will give in.
Taobao's annual project...
I'll do my best.
Then, let's wipe the slate clean
regarding what happened before.
To a successful partnership.
See?
This is his charm despite being so stubborn.
Why is he so amazing?
One,
he's vicious.
He's vicious to himself,
and he's even more vicious to the clients.
Two,
he's wise.
He knows when to advance
and when to take a step back.
Three,
he's cold.
No one knows what he is thinking.
That makes them want to win him over.
Isn't that crazy?
He sounds like
a villain.
There's no hero or villain in the workplace.
Only winners and losers.
Luan Nian
is the winner.
If you want to learn things,
you need to work under him.
I can also learn a lot from you.
If I learn from him,
I...
He won't think I'm good enough.
No one in Lime
is good enough for him.
Join us for dinner tonight.
Don't wear this outfit.
I have a nice dress for you.
Today,
I must thank Luke
(Watch on www.kisskh.is)
for all his efforts.
That's too much praise, Mr. Li.
I must thank Laiyu.
Your ad quality is excellent.
The client is also showing gratitude
and hoping for long-term collaboration among us.
Everyone, let's have a toast!
Together!
Cheers.
Shang Zhitao.
Did I remember your name right?
Yes, Mr. Li.
Come,
Ms. Shang.
It's all thanks to you for making this partnership a success.
Come.
A toast to you.
Mr. Li, I...
I don't really drink.
How can you not drink
when you're in the advertising business?
Besides,
you either drink or you don't.
Not knowing how to drink is nonsense.
Cheers.
Ms. Shang, you're indeed an exceptional woman.
Where are you from?
I'm from Harbin.
Women from the Northeast
are all attractive.
You also carry
the grace of a woman from the South.
Are you single?
Mr. Li,
where do you think I'm from?
You...
I'm from Beijing.
Let me offer you a toast on behalf of the capital's people.
Cheers.
You are...
Let me do it.
Flora,
you still need to write that report later.
Make sure you're sober.
If you submit it late,
Mr. Luan will chew you out.
That's right, Mr. Li.
I still need to write a report later.
Does Lime
allow you to leave dinner early now?
Come.
You can't leave, Flora.
Go and listen to the conference call.
It'll help with your report.
All right.
Don't answer any calls
or reply to any texts.
Let me fill your glass.
Sure. Thanks.
Director, a toast to you.
Sure.
You are quite protective
of women now.
Taking good care of female employees
is the duty of every Lime employee.
[Are you still angry at me?]
[Luan Nian, I was wrong. I can't let you go.]
Luke.
Where are Lumi and the rest?
They are sending Mr. Li and the rest back.
[Luan Nian, I was wrong. I can't let you go.]
[Are you still angry at me?]
[Clear]
Luke.
Thank you for saving me from all that drinking today.
I've learned a lot
on this business trip.
If you can't drink,
don't even take a sip.
Not everyone deserves a toast.
All right.
Let me get us a ride.
We'll walk back
to get rid of the smell of alcohol.
No need.
Put it on.
I feel warm.
Thank you, Luke.
Flora.
If a client asks whether you're single or not next time,
how will you answer?
I'll just be honest
and say I'm single.
Are you trying to tell him
that he has a chance?
Luke,
are you single?
Yes.
Are you also telling me
that I have a chance?
If you're drunk, go back and sleep.
You'll find what you want in your dream.
Luan Nian!
Zang Yao?
Are you surprised?
Why are you here?
What?
Am I not welcome here?
No.
I mean, how do you know I'm here?
Seriously.
If Chen Kuannian hadn't told me
that you were in Guangzhou on a business trip,
I wouldn't have known.
It's an urgent business trip.
I'm in a rush
and will go back tomorrow.
I'm going out to drink with Chen.
Join us for another round.
Let's go.
I'm not going.
I still have important work to do.
Don't drive if you drink.
Ask Chen or your boyfriend to drive you back.
What a party pooper.
We already broke up.
Again?
What? I'm just learning from you.
Of all things, why learn that from me?
Why did you break up?
Why are you acting like my dad?
You ask too many questions.
Enough. Just go back to work.
I'm telling you.
I'm going to Beijing next month.
You must find time to accompany me, no matter what.
All right?
Why are you going back to Beijing?
What? Am I not welcome there?
Of course, you are.
I'll treat you to dinner when you're back.
You two
were walking along the Pearl River late at night.
Tao,
I think something might happen
between you and your boss.
What?
Didn't you say
he helped you deflect drinks and got you out of a tight spot
and gave you his jacket?
That's because he is a gentleman.
Is Luan Nian handsome?
The kind of roguishly handsome type.
Moreover, he has many women around him.
You're right.
A high-quality elite bachelor
will be surrounded by women.
But don't give up.
You aren't bad.
You have a nice body, and you're pretty.
That's enough, Sun Yu.
I still have a report to rush.
I'll talk to you later.
[Luan Nian: Are you not going to return my jacket?]
[Which room are you in?]
Luke.
Sorry for disturbing you so late at night.
Thank you for lending me your jacket.
Come in.
No.
I shouldn't enter your room.
If someone sees us so late at night,
it will be hard to explain.
It'll damage your reputation.
Are you from the past or what?
Give this to Lumi tomorrow morning.
What are you thinking?
I...
I think
it might be inconvenient if someone is in your room.
Am I some sort of
pervert
in your mind?
No.
If you have time to do that,
you should reflect on your work again.
In the workplace, only results can speak for you.
Go back and think about
how to improve.
Go back.
I'll go back and reflect on my work
and send it to you.
Please guide me.
Why are you sending it to me?
Am I your mentor or what?
You're still not leaving?
[Canton Hotel]
It's done, sir.
Thank you.
Boss.
Here you go.
Is it done?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
We got the deal,
but we're in trouble again when coming up with a proposal later.
Lumi,
can I become the assistant to the PM for this project?
Sure.
If you think you can handle it, just go for it.
I'm back.
Tao, you're back.
Just in time.
Lei,
I've not seen Shang Zhitao come back for dinner
for a long time.
Shang Zhitao?
Hello.
Lei.
I'm Zhang Lei.
Hello, Lei.
I've finally met our landlord.
Wow,
what a feast.
Sit down, quickly.
I didn't help out at all today.
Let me do the dishes, all right?
How much should I pay?
Who should I transfer to?
No need.
Let Lei and me treat everyone.
We must take care of each other when we're living outside.
Most importantly, it doesn't cost much.
Let's have a toast first
to celebrate our landlord's return.
Welcome!
Thank you, everyone.
Lei, you've been working abroad for two months.
Right?
The project was running for too long.
I've not come home for two months.
Thanks, babe.
I'm so exhausted.
But I can see that you three are getting along well.
Thank you.
Of course.
These two people are nice.
They are
the stars in the sky
compared to those two who only deserve to live in the basement.
Really?
Shang Zhitao,
it's our first meeting.
I didn't prepare any gift for you.
Well,
I'll give you
a discount of 100 yuan on your rent.
Really?
You didn't give me the same favor.
You took care of the house well.
I'll give you a 50-yuan discount.
Not bad.
Everyone will get a 100-yuan discount!
Thank you, Lei.
Thank you, Landlord.
Cheers!
Hurry and eat.
Lei.
Thank you.
You can hold your liquor.
- Lei. - Cheers!
Thanks, Landlord.
The meat is ready.
Do you still want that discount?
Flora,
have you reminded Luke
to approve the business trip expenses?
Why hasn't it been approved yet?
I'm going to make a claim on Monday.
I sent it to him, but he didn't give me a reply.
Rush him again.
Otherwise, just call him.
Sure.
Don't be scared.
Rushing your boss will help you gain experience.
I'm counting on you.
Bye.
Hello, Luke.
[Shang Zhitao]
Sorry for disturbing you this late.
I have a few things to confirm with you.
Also, I need you to approve
an OA budget.
What's the rush for payment?
Even if I approve it at night,
will the finance department pay you?
[Re: Budget Approval - Fund request. Payment approved.]
[Send]
[Luke: Payment approved.]
Thank you.
I've learned a lot.
Thank you for the hard work.
I'll go back and reflect on my work
and send it to you.
Please guide me.
Do you need anything else from me?
There's more,
but it's not urgent.
It's late.
I won't disturb your rest any further.
[Shang Zhitao]
[Luan Nian]
Luke.
Are you going to disturb me tomorrow, then?
I left some documents at the office.
I'm afraid you might not see them.
I'm at the office now.
What else do you need me for?
Tell me everything in one go.
Also,
the filming venue needs your approval.
I sent it to your secretary.
I'll confirm with the client on Monday.
Also,
I sent the filming material and budget
usage progress to you.
They require your approval.
Go and find Jack tomorrow.
Then,
there's nothing else for now.
Sorry
for disturbing you.
It's all right.
Thank you for the hard work.
Good night.
[Shang Zhitao]
You're still not hanging up?
Are you eavesdropping?
Workplace etiquette.
The boss should hang up first.
Workplace etiquette?
Fine.
I should have hung up sooner.
Patience
is probably her strength.
Are you still working so late at night?
Yes.
I'm rushing my boss to approve a budget.
How is it? Are you done?
Done.
That's great.
In my opinion,
being in a workplace is like being in a relationship.
The boss tortures me thousands of times,
but I still treat him like my first love.
My experience tells me
that first loves don't end well.
You must not have any feelings
toward your boss.
Don't scare her.
A boss isn't God.
He just has a few more years of experience
compared to you.
You work so hard.
I'm sure your efforts will be seen one day.
I'm not as hardworking as my boss.
He is still working overtime in the office now.
He's talented and hardworking.
Going to work
feels like the college entrance examination for me.
I dare not get a single question wrong.
Working
is not like running a marathon.
You don't have to be on the same path as your boss.
Just be a blade of grass.
Even if he has a temper,
you can still grow on the ground.
Bouncing back after a storm.
A rookie's greatest strength isn't experience,
but the vigor to grow wildly.
Moss flowers as small as a grain of rice
also bloom like the peony.
You are just like a seed now.
No one can stop you once you grow out of the ground.
Well said.
I heard it from a scholar...
I mean, I learned it.
Blooming like the roses or something.
Peony.
I'm telling you.
Hiring people isn't like opening a mystery box.
No one will hire you if you don't have some hidden skills.
Exactly.
I can see
that your hidden skills just haven't been developed yet.
Is that so?
That's right.
How great.
If luck can be ranked,
my luck must be ranked first.
No matter how hard my job is,
I still have my friends to support me.
I'm back to my energetic self again.
You're a good student.
Next meal's on you.
No.
I'm not paying.
You'll never amount to much.
Lei.
Next meal's on you.
Don't look at me.
It's still your treat.
Your treat?
My treat?
Your treat.
Mala crawfish.
[Lime Advertising]
The coffee machine is over there.
Your office is quite impressive.
I finally realized what's wrong with this.
This proposal lacks a concrete approach to address the pain points.
Didn't you ask me to amend it
to increase the value?
That's right.
This version is too conceptual.
It's too abstract.
Do you understand?
But our direction previously
was focusing on Mulanshuo and Taobao's collaboration
to show the advantage
of fast delivery, powered by their extensive logistics networks.
If we suddenly change to something else,
won't it
create confusion about the project's focus?
Moreover, the whole direction
- is different. - Are you teaching me how to do things?
Regardless of the project's direction,
we must improve it
to make it perfect.
Ask the creative division to come up with a few drafts
so we can compare them.
You are a rookie. You might not know
that creativity comes from making amendments.
Why don't I
ask Luke's opinion?
If you ask your boss about everything,
what's the point of having us?
Besides,
there'll never be a final draft in a good proposal.
It can always be amended before it is shot.
Flora.
Go and ask Luke.
Ask the decision maker.
Lumi, what's the meaning of this?
I mean what I said.
Luke approved this project's creative idea.
If he finds out how you waste his efforts,
who do you think will be in trouble?
A rookie?
Haven't you been a rookie before?
If you keep making amendments,
can you take responsibility
for delaying the progress?
Well,
let me ask Luke.
I'll take responsibility if anything happens.
Come in.
Luke.
It's time for the execution phase of the creative idea.
There's a delay in the progress.
There have been ongoing opinions.
Didn't I approve the proposal?
Why are there so many opinions?
That's not an issue.
I'm just worried that our direction is wrong.
How many drafts have been made?
Seven or eight drafts.
Completing a project on schedule
is also an important assessment criterion for a PM.
I know.
It's my mistake.
These are the revision comments.
Do you want to take a look?
I'll follow up on the progress.
No.
Go back and create a work group.
Anyone can raise their opinions in the group.
Every round of communication going forward
must be recorded in an email.
Wouldn't it be too formal
to record every conversation in an email?
Formal?
Is the workplace some kind of child's play?
Having it in writing
is what protects you.
Got it.
Can I add you to the group?
You don't need to speak.
Summarize the work discussed in the group and send it via email.
The email must be concise. Highlight the important points in red.
CC the related people.
Got it.
I'll do as you say.
The golden rule of workplace communication
is that whoever proposes must take responsibility.
The person with an opinion must provide a solution.
What if they just mention it casually?
Get him to shut up, then.
No need for nonsense in the workplace.
You only need results.
I got it. Thank you.
I've learned something else.
Don't thank me just yet.
Have you prepared yourself for the commercial shoot?
Can I really go there?
Lumi recommended you.
She specifically requested that you go.
This time, the filming location is in the mountains.
The conditions are quite harsh.
Can you do it?
I can.
I don't mind the dirty work.
Handling the dirty work isn't something to brag about.
You can do all the work,
but without the result, it still means nothing.
- Because... - Only results speak for you.
I understand.
I'll charge you a tuition fee next time.
Goodbye, Luke.
Hello. Can I clean this room?
Sure.
What is this?
It's probably from the typewriter.
It's probably useless now.
No, it's not. Give it to me.
Okay.
Thanks, Madam.
How dare you
wear my man's clothes?
I...
I did not.
♪One look is all it takes to find the right person♪
♪One lifetime is all it takes to commemorate this love♪
♪Whatever remains will be the proof♪
♪If it never crosses your mind♪
♪The tide as I turn back♪
♪Is just formless attraction♪
♪Your silhouette is closing in♪
♪Your breathing grows clear♪
♪Too many distractions in this world♪
♪I would rather forget myself♪
♪Just this moment♪
♪One look is all it takes to find the right person♪
♪One lifetime is all it takes to commemorate this love♪
♪If you miss it, just save the traces♪
♪If your tears fall on their own♪
♪Followed by our hearts beating to the same rhythm♪
♪Will you listen to it♪
♪Or will you reply to me in silence?♪
♪Your silhouette is closing in♪
♪Your breathing grows clear♪
♪Too many distractions in this world♪
♪I would rather forget myself♪
♪All I want is to lose myself in this moment♪
♪Your aloofness masks your vulnerability♪
♪I hide my nervousness in the corner♪
♪Too many hurdles in this world♪
♪Even one moment can keep us warm♪
♪Just this moment♪
♪All right?♪